Guide to the Archives of Irish America Vertical Files AIA.013
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- T
  - The Traditional Irish Musicians Association, Inc., 1973 (Box 19)
  - Translations (Playbill Program), 1995 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Travel Brochures, 1958-1980 (Box 19)
  - Trinity College: The Book of Kells Collection, 1995 (Box 19)
  - Troy Tribute to James Connolly, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Turning Points in Irish History Lecture, 2006-2007 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Tuxedo Ballroom, 1960 (Box 19)
- U
  - U2, 1987 (Box 19)
  - "Ulysses in Hand: The Rosenbach Manuscript", 2000 (Box 19)
  - Understanding the Irish in New Jersey, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Photographs, undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Unite Ireland Bumper Stickers, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - United Arts Club Limited, 1980 (Box 19)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Irish American Studies Committee, 1988, 1997 (Box 19)
  - United Irish American Immigration Committee, circa 1986 (Box 19)
  - United Irish American Societies of the Delaware Valley, 1988 (Box 19)
  - United Irish Counties Association of New York, 1987, 2011 (Box 19, Box 42, Folder 9)
  - United Irish Counties Association of New York, Inc. - 109th Dinner Dance, 2013 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - United Irish Counties Association of New York, Inc. - Forty Eighth Annual Feis, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - United Irish Counties Association of New York, Inc. - Ninety First Annual Dinner Dance, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - United Irish Counties Association of New York, Inc. - Second Grand Festival, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Unity -Newsletter of the Irish American Unity Conference, 2006-2007 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - University College Cork, 1992-1997 (Box 19)
  - University College Dublin, undated (Box 19)
  - University College Dublin -- Clinton Institute -- "Supporting the Next Generation of the Irish Diaspora", 2014 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - University College Dublin in North America, 1985-1997 (Box 19)
  - University of Notre Dame, circa 2004-2005 (Box 20)
  - University of St. Thomas, 1997 (Box 20)
  - University of St. Thomas -- Center for Irish Studies, 1999-2004 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - U.S.-Ireland Alliance, 2000 (Box 20)
  - U.S. Irish (Publication), undated (Box 20)
- V
  - Veterans Corps 69th Infantry Regiment, 1974, 1992-1997 (Box 20)
  - Villanova University, 1993 (Box 20)
  - The Vinegar Hill History and Preservation League, 1998 (Box 20)
  - "The Voice of Ireland", circa 1990-1999 (Box 20)
  - Voices Envisioned - Memories Made in Northern Ireland, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- W
  - Wake Forest University Press, 1994 (Box 20)
  - Wallace, Mike, undated (Box 20)
  - Walsh, Maureen -- Photograph and Clipping, 1955 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Walton's Theory of Irish Songs and Ballads, undated (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Ward, Michael, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - W.B. Yeats Drama Foundation, 1991-1993 (Box 20)
  - W.B. Yeats Society of New York, 1991, 2020 (Box 20, Box 55, Folder 9)
  - We Built This City, 2013 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - W.E. Jackson & Co., circa 1997 (Box 20)
  - Web-Based Irish and Irish American Businesses, 1996-2000 (Box 20)
  - Weddings, 1967 (Box 20)
  - Weekend Trips (Irish-Themed), 1981, 1999 (Box 20)
  - Westchester People's Action Coalition, Inc. (WESPAC), undated (Box 20)
  - West Belfast Economic Forum, 2000 (Box 20)
  - West Orange St. Patrick's Day Parade, 2012 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Who Do We Think We Are? Economics Family-Style (Glucksman Ireland House), undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - The Wild Geese, 1982-2005 (Box 20, Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Wood, Ida E., undated (Box 20)
  - Worcester County St. Patrick's Parade - Sights and Sound of Ireland, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - The World of Hibernia: promotional literature and mailings, 1995 (Box 20, Box 36, Folder 13)
  - The Writings of Bobby Sands: Irish Northern Aid I.P.O.W. Committee, New York, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Oversize
  - The 3rd Annual Festival of Irish Theatre Poster, 2010 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 28)
  - 10th Annual Irish Traditional Music Festival Poster, 1991 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 29)
  - 33rd Annual East Durham Irish Festival, 2010 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 20)
  - Album Liners, undated (Oversize 22)
  - The American Irish Newsletter, 1987 (Oversize 22)
  - Ancient Order of the Hibernians of American Certificate of Membership, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 22)
  - Art Exhibitions, 2007 (Oversize 22)
  - Clan Na Gael of Long Island - felt banner, 1928, 1967 (Oversize 23)
  - Columban Fathers, 1960 (Oversize 22)
  - Festivals: New York City and New York State, 1989-1995, undated (Oversize 22)
  - Festivals: United States (outside NYC and Washington D.C.), 1994-1996 (Oversize 22)
  - Freedom Struggle by the IRA Poster, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 068, Folder 21)
  - From Two Different Shores: Asian and Irish Immigrant Women Poster, 1991 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 19)
  - Gaelic League Newspaper Articles, 1966 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 27)
  - Genealogy, undated (Oversize 22)
  - Harper's Weekly Newspaper - St Patrick in New York cartoon, 1870 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 25)
  - Holiday Magazine, 1968 (Box Shared Tamiment 068, Folder 22)
  - "If They'd Only Move Old Ireland Over Here", undated
    - Poster (Oversize 22)
    - Digital Materials, TW_AIA_013_ER_5
  - Illustrated London News: Supplement, 1844 (Oversize 22)
  - Ireland on Parade: Irish Police Band Poster, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 23)
  - Irish Americans for Kerry Edwards poster, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 25)
  - The Irish Rebel Theatre, circa 1980 (Oversize 22)
  - Knights of the Red Branch Poster, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 26)
  - Life Magazine, 1963 (Oversize 24)
  - Look Magazine, Dec 1962 (Oversize 24)
  - Merchant Advertisement: Shamrock Valencias, Orange County Caifornia (label from a crate?), undated (Oversize 24)
    Provenance
    Originally in Patrick Daughton Collection AIA 055
  - Moloney, Michael (Mick), 2004 (Oversize 24)
  - A Musical Celebration of International Human Rights Day poster, 1993 (Box Shared Tamiment 068, Folder 30)
  - Sheet Music and Lyrics [3 folders] Titles include: The Four Leaf Shamrock of Glenore, I've Got the Blues for the Wearing of the Green, My Wild Irish Rose, All That I Want is in Ireland, Rose of Kilkenny, Kathleen Mavournee n, Soldiers of Erin: The Rallying Song of the Irish Volunteers, The Irish Lads in Blue, I Dreamt that I Dwelt in Marble Halls, undated (Oversize 24)
    Scope and Content Note
    Titles include: The Four Leaf Shamrock of Glenore, I've Got the Blues for the Wearing of the Green, My Wild Irish Rose, All That I Want is in Ireland, Rose of Kilkenny, Kathleen Mavourneen, Soldiers of Erin: The Rallying Song of the Irish Volunteers, The Irish Lads in Blue, I Dreamt that I Dwelt in Marble Halls
  - "New York, New York: The Neighborhoods", 1988 (Oversize 24)
  - New York Post, 2001 (Oversize 24)
  - Newspaper Clippings - The Advocate, Roscommon Herald, 1964, 1973, 1978 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper Clipping - Final Tribute to Cardinal John J. O'Connor, 2000 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Obituaries, 1963-1976 (Oversize 24)
  - Observe the Sons of Ulster Marching Towards the Somme (play poster), undated (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 24)
  - O'Dwyer, Paul (New York News Magazin e article), 1975 (Oversize 24)
  - O'Neill's Irish Pictorial, 1859 (Oversize 24)
  - Plan of the Town of Arklow, undated (Oversize 24)
  - The Provisional Government of the Irish Republic: 50th Anniversary Calendar, 1966 (Oversize 24)
  - Representative and Mrs. Hugh L. Carey and Family Ask the Blessing of St. Patrick Poster, 1968 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 18)
  - "The Riots at New York -- The Rioters Burning and Sacking the Colored Orphan Asylum" from Harper's Weekly, 1863 (Oversize 24)
  - Roman Catholic Diocese of Brooklyn, 1953 (Oversize 22)
  - Saint Patrick's Day Parade Celebration: Official Program, 1964-1987 (Oversize 25)
  - The Saturday Evening Post, 1963 (Oversize 25)
  - Sisters of St. Joseph:"The Flowering Staff: The Story of the First Century of the Congregation of the Sisters of Saint Joseph in the Diocese of Brookly, New York, 1856-1956" (Oversize 25)
  - Small Productions: "Of Pubs and Paradise", 2004 (Oversize 25)
  - When Irish Eyes are Smiling (Associated News Service Poster), 1928 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 26)